RG 005:036, Office of the Governor: Ella Grasso (1975-1980)
Connecticut State Library
- Part I Subject Files, 1972-1977
  - Labor (Box 200)
    - Br-Bz (B) (Box 201)
    - C (B) (Box 201)
    - D (B) (Box 201)
    - E (B) (Box 201)
    - F (B) (Box 202)
    - G (B) (Box 202)
    - H (B) (Box 202)
    - I, J (B) (Box 202)
    - K (B) (Box 203)
    - L (B) (Box 203)
    - Ma - Maz (B) (Box 203)
    - Mc - Mz (B) (Box 204)
    - N (B) (Box 204)
    - O, P (B) (Box 204)
    - Q, R (B) (Box 204)
    - S (B) (Box 205)
    - T (B) (Box 205)
    - U, V, W (B) (Box 205)
    - X, Y, Z (B) (Box 205)
  - Labor (Box 206)
    - Apprenticeship Council (Box 206)
    - Budget (Box 206)
    - Bulletin (Box 206)
    - CETA (B) (Box 206)
    - CETA (Comp. Employment - Training Act) (B) (Box 206)
    - Commission to Study & Make Recommendations Concerning Workmen’s Compensation Systems (O) (Box 207)
    - Compensation Commission (O) (Box 207)
    - Compensation Laws (B) (Box 207)
    - Department Bulletin (Box 207)
    - Employment Security (Box 207)
    - Employment Security Advisory Council (Box 207)
    - Employment Security Board (O) (Box 207)
    - Employment & Security of Review (B) (Box 207)
    - Federal Unemployment Tax Act (B) (Box 207)
    - Improving Occupational Regulation (Box 207)
    - Labor Relations Board (Box 207)
    - Mag. Letter #36 - 40 hr. Work Week (Box 207)
    - Manpower (B) (Box 207)
    - Manpower (B) (Box 207)
    - Manpower Services Council (Box 208)
    - Meditation & Arbitration (B) (Box 208)
    - Misc. Material (Box 208)
    - Occupational Licensing (B) (Box 209)
    - Occupational Safety & Health Act (B) (Box 209)
    - OSHA, Committee on (Box 209)
    - OSHA Memo on Training Seminar (Box 209)
    - News Clippings (Box 209)
    - Patient Worker Regulations (Box 209)
    - Panding (Box 209)
    - Press Release, Employment Security (Box 209)
    - Press Releases from Governor’s Office (Box 209)
    - Pro Santaguida (B) (Box 209)
    - Re-employment (B) (Box 209)
    - State Labor Council (Box 209)
    - Unemployment (B) (Box 209)
      - A - K (B) (Box 209)
      - K - Z (B) (Box 209)
    - Unemployment, Milford Office Closing, Mag. #38 (B) (Box 210)
    - Unemployment Tax (Box 210)
    - U.S. Department of Labor (Box 210)
    - Workmen’s Compensation (Box 210)
  - Labor - Workmen’s Compensation Commission/Appointments (Box 211)
  - Landscape Architects (B) (Box 211)
  - Land Surveyor (Box 211)
  - Language (Box 211)
  - Law Enforcement (B) (Box 211)
  - Law Enforcement Assistance Administration (LEAA) (B) (Box 211)
  - LEAA Appropriations Bill - Letters to Congressional Delegation (O) (Box 211)
  - LEAA Grant (B), 1975 September 18 (Box 211)
  - Law Library (B) (Box 211)
  - League of Women Voters (Box 211)
  - Legal (Box 212)
    - Advertising by Lawyers (Box 212)
    - Aid (B) (Box 212)
    - American Bar Association (Box 212)
    - Assistance Corporation (B) (Box 212)
    - Avcollie Case (Judge Cohen) (B) (Box 212)
    - Bernard Avcollie/S. Cohen (B) (Box 212)
    - Blue Laws (B) (Box 212)
    - Blue Laws (Sunday) Mag. #16 (B) (Box 212)
    - Blue Laws #16 Revised (B) (Box 212)
    - Blue Laws #16 Revised Again (B), 1977 February 23 (Box 212)
    - Blue Laws #16 Revised, 1977 September (Box 212)
    - Bridgeport Bar Association (Box 212)
    - Bridgeport Jail - State of Conn. vs. David Friend (Box 212)
    - Capital Punishment (B) (Box 212)
    - Conn. Bar Association (Box 212)
    - Extradition (By Person Being Extradited) (O) (Box 213)
    - Judge Tedesco (B) (Box 213)
    - Misc. Material (Box 213)
    - New London County Bar Association (Box 213)
    - Peter Reilly (B) (Box 213)
    - Peter Reilly Case #56 (B), 1977 October (Box 213)
    - Peter Reilly #3 (B) (Box 213)
    - Publications (Box 213)
    - Services (Legal) (B) (Box 213)
    - Services (Legal) Advisory Council (B) (Box 213)
    - Youthful Offenders #6 (B), 1977 August 15 (Box 214)
    - Youthful Offenders Letters with no Addresses (B) (Box 214)
  - Legal Matter (Box 214)
    - A, B (B) (Box 214)
    - C, D (B) (Box 215)
    - E, F (B) (Box 215)
    - G, H (B) (Box 216)
    - I, J, K (B) (Box 216)
    - L, M (B) (Box 217)
    - N, O, P (B) (Box 217)
    - Q, R, S (B) (Box 218)
    - T, U, V, W, X, Y, Z (B) (Box 218)
  - Legislation (Box 218)
    - A (B) (Box 218)
    - B (B) (Box 218)
    - C (B) (Box 219)
    - D (B) (Box 219)
    - E (Box 219)
    - F (B) (Box 219)
    - G (B) (Box 219)
    - H (B) (Box 219)
    - I, J (B) (Box 219)
    - K (B) (Box 219)
    - M (B) (Box 219)
    - N (B) (Box 219)
    - O, P (B) (Box 219)
    - Q, R (B) (Box 219)
    - S (B) (Box 219)
    - T (B) (Box 219)
    - U, V (B) (Box 219)
    - W (B) (Box 219)
  - Legislation (Box 219)
    - Banking (B) (Box 219)
    - Bilingual Education (B) (Box 219)
    - Bottle Bill (B) (Box 219)
    - Energy/S. 2162 (O) (Box 219)
    - Ethics (Box 219)
    - Fires and Quits Bill (B) (Box 219)
    - Letters to Congressional Delegation PAT’s S. 1967, H.R. 1300, S. 1587 (B) (Box 219)
    - Misc. Material (Box 220)
    - Public Works Employment Acts (B) (Box 220)
    - Social Security Bill HR 5322 - letter to Congressional delegation (B) (Box 220)
    - Social Security HR 7200, letter to Congressional delegation (B) (Box 220)
    - Water Company Lands (B) (Box 220)
  - Lego (Box 220)
  - Letters to Congress (O) (Box 220)
  - Library (B) (Box 220)
  - Library (Box 220)
    - A (B) (Box 220)
    - B (B) (Box 220)
    - C (B) (Box 220)
    - D (B) (Box 220)
    - E (B) (Box 220)
    - F (B) (Box 220)
    - G (B) (Box 220)
    - H (B) (Box 220)
    - I, J (B) (Box 220)
    - K (B) (Box 220)
    - L (B) (Box 220)
    - M (B) (Box 220)
    - N (B) (Box 221)
    - O (B) (Box 221)
    - P (B) (Box 221)
    - Q, R (B) (Box 221)
    - S (B) (Box 221)
    - T (B) (Box 221)
    - U, V (B) (Box 221)
    - W, X, Y, Z (B) (Box 221)
  - Library (Box 221)
    - Conn. Library Association (Box 221)
    - Library Line (B) (Box 221)
    - Misc. Material (Box 221)
    - State Library Budget Request (B) (Box 221)
    - State Library Committee (B) (Box 221)
    - State Library Press Release (Box 221)
  - Licensing Board (B) (Box 221)
  - Lieutenant Governor (B) (Box 221)
  - Lipsett (B) (Box 221)
  - Liquor (B) (Box 221)
  - Liquor Control Commission (B) (Box 221)
  - Litchfield Hills Regional Planning Agency (Box 221)
  - Lobbying (B) (Box 221)
  - Local Matter (Box 221)
    - A - J (B) (Box 221)
    - K - Z (B) (Box 222)
  - Logging (Box 222)
  - Longo (Box 222)
  - Mail Report (Box 222)
  - Mallview Apartments - Waterbury (Box 222)
  - Maps (I) (Box 222)
  - March of Dimes (B) (Box 222)
  - Marketing Authority (Box 222)
  - Martin Luther King Day (Box 222)
  - Mass Mailings (B) (Box 222)
  - Mayaguez Con. (B) (Box 222)
  - Mayaguez Incident (B) (Box 222)
  - Mayors and First Selectmen Letters (O) (Box 222)
  - McKinney (Box 222)
  - Medal of Honor (B) (Box 222)
  - Medical Examining Board (O) (Box 222)
  - Medicare (B) (Box 222)
  - Mediocolegal Investigations (B) (Box 222)
  - Meditation (T.M.) (B) (Box 222)
  - Memorandums (Box 222)
  - Memos to Ment (Box 222)
  - Memos to and from Plant (Box 222)
  - Memos to and from Shepard (Box 222)
  - Mental Health (Box 223)
    - A (B) (Box 223)
    - B (B) (Box 223)
    - C (Box 223)
    - D (B) (Box 223)
    - E (B) (Box 223)
    - F (B) (Box 223)
    - Ga - Go (B) (Box 223)
    - Go - Gz (B) (Box 223)
    - Ha - He (B) (Box 223)
    - Ho - Hz (B) (Box 223)
    - I, J (B) (Box 223)
    - K (B) (Box 224)
    - L (B) (Box 224)
    - M (B) (Box 224)
    - N (B) (Box 224)
    - O (B) (Box 224)
    - P (B) (Box 224)
    - Q, R (B) (Box 224)
    - S (B) (Box 224)
    - T (B) (Box 224)
    - U, V (B) (Box 224)
    - W, X, Y, Z (B) (Box 225)
  - Mental Health (Box 225)
    - Alcoholic Clinic, Bridgeport, Mag. June 25 (Box 225)
    - Annual Report, 1973-1974 (Box 225)
    - Annual Report, 1974-1975 (Box 225)
    - Association (of Conn.) (Box 225)
    - Bibb Matta (B) (Box 225)
    - Bridgeport Detoxification (B) (Box 225)
    - Budget (Box 225)
    - Commissioner (B) (Box 225)
    - Connecticut Valley Hospital (B) (Box 225)
    - Connecticut House, Middletown (B) (Box 225)
    - Detoxification Units (B) (Box 225)
    - Fairfield Hills Hospital (B) (Box 225)
    - Fairfield Hills Mag./Safety Standards (B) (Box 225)
    - High Meadows (Box 225)
    - Hungerford Hospital (B) (Box 225)
    - Institute of Living (Box 225)
    - Kendal Memos (Box 226)
    - Licensing Hospitals for Mentally Ill (Box 226)
    - Mental Deficient (O) (Box 226)
    - Misc. Material (Box 226)
    - New England Children’s Mental Health Task Force (Box 226)
    - News Clippings (Box 226)
    - Norwich State Hospital (B) (Box 226)
    - Pending (B) (Box 226)
    - Personnel (Box 226)
    - Plant (I) (Box 226)
    - President’s Commission on Mental Health (B) (Box 226)
    - Press Releases from Governor’s Office (Box 226)
    - Pro-Shepherd (B) (Box 226)
    - Psychiatry’s Pay (B) (Box 226)
    - Shepard Nomination, State Board of Mental Health (I) (Box 226)
    - State Board of Mental Health (B) (Box 226)
    - State Plan, 1975 (Box 226)
    - Undercliff (B) (Box 226)
    - Undercliff/Mag. Card (B), 1976 June 6 (Box 226)
    - Undercliff/Mag. (B), 1975 June 18 (Box 226)
    - Wheeler Affiliates (B) (Box 226)
    - Whiting Forensic Institute (B) (Box 226)
    - Gueger File (Box 226)
  - Mental Illness - Misc. Information (Box 227)
  - Metric Coordinating Council (B) (Box 227)
  - Metropolitan District Commission (B) (Box 227)
  - Michigan (Box 227)
  - Military (Box 227)
    - A (B) (Box 227)
    - B (B) (Box 227)
    - C (B) (Box 227)
    - D (B) (Box 227)
    - E (B) (Box 227)
    - F (B) (Box 227)
    - G (B) (Box 227)
    - H (B) (Box 227)
    - I, J (B) (Box 227)
    - K (B) (Box 227)
    - L (B) (Box 227)
    - M (B) (Box 227)
    - N (B) (Box 227)
    - O (B) (Box 227)
    - P (B) (Box 227)
    - Q, R (B) (Box 227)
    - S (B) (Box 227)
    - T (B) (Box 227)
    - U, V (B) (Box 227)
    - W, X, Y, Z (B) (Box 227)
  - Military (Box 227)
    - Adjustment General (Box 227)
    - Air Force (B) (Box 227)
    - Air National Guard (Box 227)
    - Army (B) (Box 228)
    - Army Corps of Engineers (Box 228)
    - Army Corps of Engineers, Water Resources Development (Box 228)
    - Christmas Message (B), 1977 (Box 229)
    - Civil Air Patrol (B) (Box 229)
    - Civil Preparedness (Box 229)
    - Coast Guard (B) (Box 229)
    - Coast Guard Academy (Box 229)
    - Coast Guard Commendation (O) (Box 229)
    - Coast Guard, Environmental Impact Statement for Deepwater Parts (Box 229)
    - Governor’s Foot Guard (B) (Box 229)
    - Governor’s Horse Guard (Box 229)
    - Military Academics (B) (Box 229)
    - Military Staff (Box 229)
    - National Guard (B) (Box 229)
    - National Guard Camp (B) (Box 230)
    - Naval Academy (B) (Box 230)
    - Navy (Box 230)
    - Staff Christmas party (O), 1976 July 1 (Box 230)
    - State Emergency Operations Plan (Box 230)
    - Submarine Base (Box 230)
  - Mining (Box 230)
  - Minorities (B) (Box 230)
  - Minority Contractors (B) (Box 230)
  - Miscellaneous: Correspondence (Box 230)
    - A (B) (Box 230)
    - Ba - Beril (B) (Box 231)
    - Brian - Bz (B) (Box 231)
    - Ca - Car (B) (Box 232)
    - Cas - Coh (B) (Box 232)
    - Cole - Cz (B) (Box 232)
    - D (B) (Box 233)
    - E (B) (Box 233)
    - F (B) (Box 233)
    - Ga - Giv (B) (Box 234)
    - Gla - Gz (B) (Box 234)
    - H (B) (Box 235)
    - I (B) (Box 235)
    - J (B) (Box 235)
    - K (B) (Box 236)
    - L (Box 236)
    - Ma - Mazz (B) (Box 237)
    - McAL - Mz (B) (Box 237)
    - N (B) (Box 238)
    - O (B) (Box 238)
    - Pa - Pett (B) (Box 238)
    - Pfan - Pz (B) (Box 239)
    - Q (B) (Box 239)
    - R (B) (Box 239)
    - Sa - Shus (B) (Box 240)
    - Sidd - Sz (B) (Box 241)
    - T (B) (Box 241)
    - U (B) (Box 242)
    - V (B) (Box 242)
    - W (B) (Box 242)
    - X, Y, Z (B) (Box 242)
  - Mobil homes (B) (Box 243)
  - Moffet (Box 243)
  - Mune, John (Box 243)
  - Mune, Mrs. (Box 243)
  - Mortgages (Box 243)
  - Mother-of-the-year (B) (Box 243)
  - Motion Picture (B) (Box 243)
  - Motor Cycles (B) (Box 243)
  - Motor Vehicles: (Box 243)
    - A (B) (Box 243)
    - B (B) (Box 243)
    - C (B) (Box 243)
    - D (B) (Box 244)
    - E (B) (Box 244)
    - F (B) (Box 244)
    - G (B) (Box 244)
    - H (B) (Box 244)
    - I, J (B) (Box 244)
    - K (B) (Box 245)
    - L (B) (Box 245)
    - M (Box 245)
    - N (B) (Box 245)
    - O (B) (Box 245)
    - P (B) (Box 245)
    - Q, R (B) (Box 246)
    - S (B) (Box 246)
    - T (B) (Box 246)
    - U, V (B) (Box 246)
    - W (B) (Box 246)
    - X, Y, Z (B) (Box 246)
  - Motor Vehicle (Box 247)
    - AAMV Bulletin (Box 247)
    - Ansonia Office (Box 247)
    - Anti-Pac (B) (Box 247)
    - Bulletin (Box 247)
    - Commissioner (Box 247)
    - Dek Electro Study (Box 247)
    - Driver’s Licenses (B) (Box 247)
    - Dunn School Buses (Box 247)
    - Fleet Administrator (Box 247)
    - Inspection (B) (Box 247)
    - License Plates (B) (Box 247)
    - Manuals (Box 247)
    - Memos to and from Muzio (Box 247)
    - Memos to and from Pac (Box 247)
    - Misc. Material (Box 247)
    - Motorcycle Helmet Laws (B) (Box 247)
    - Noise Pollution (Box 247)
    - Press Releases (Box 247)
    - Press Release from Governor’s Office (Box 247)
    - Pro-Pac (B) (Box 247)
    - Putnam (B) (Box 247)
    - Reflectorized Plates (Box 247)
    - Registration Fee (B) (Box 247)
    - School Buses (B) (Box 247)
    - Statistics (Box 247)
    - Winsted Branch (B) (Box 247)
  - Mount Holyoke (Box 247)
  - Mount Sinai (Box 247)
  - Municipal Assistance Program - Mag. Card (O) (Box 247)
  - Municipal Finance Forum (Box 247)
  - Municipal Matter (Box 247)
  - Muscular Dystrophy (Box 248)
  - Mystic Seaport (Box 248)
  - National Alliance of Businessmen (Box 248)
  - National Articles (Box 248)
  - NAACP (Box 248)
  - National Association of Coordinators (Box 248)
  - National Conference on Christians & Jews (B) (Box 248)
  - National Defense (B) (Box 248)
  - National Federation of Democratic Women (Box 248)
  - National Governor’s Association (Box 249)
  - National Governor’s Conference (Box 250)
  - National Governor’s Conference (Box 250)
    - Bulletin (Box 250)
    - Federal/State Information Letter (Box 250)
  - National Governor’s Conference
    - Governor’s Energy Project (Box 251)
    - Memorandums’ (Box 251)
    - Memos (Box 251)
    - Printed Letters (B) (Box 251)
    - Special Letters (Box 251)
    - Task Force on Medicaid (Box 251)
    - Washington D.C. Winter Meeting, 1975 February 18-20 (Box 251)
  - National Science Foundation (Box 252)
  - National Training 7 Development Service (Box 252)
  - National Youth Sport Program (Box 252)
  - Nation’s Cities (Box 252)
  - Nature Conservancy Board (Box 252)
  - Naturalized Citizens (Box 252)
  - Naturalized Citizen Letter (Box 252)
  - Neiditz (Box 252)
  - New America (Box 252)
  - New Britain (Box 252)
  - New Britain Firefighters (B) (Box 252)
  - New Britain Memorial Hospital (Box 252)
  - New Britain Museum (Box 252)
  - New Britain Talk (Box 252)
  - New Citizen (Box 253)
  - New England (Box 253)
  - New England Congressional Caucus (Box 253)
  - New England Council (Box 253)
  - New England Economic Project (Box 253)
  - New England energy Authority (Box 253)
  - New England Fuel Institute (Box 253)
  - New England Governor’s Conference (Box 253)
  - New England Governor’s Conference (Box 253)
    - Date, 1974 (Box 253)
    - Energy (Box 253)
  - New England Governor’s Conference (Box 254)
    - Letters to Canadian Prime Minister (B) (Box 254)
    - Restoration of Salmon (Box 254)
    - Tourism (Box 254)
    - Grade (Box 254)
  - New England Governor’s Reception, Mayflower Hotel, 1975 February 18 (Box 254)
  - New England Governor’s Summer Meeting (Box 254)
  - New England Municipal Center (Box 254)
  - New England Regional Commission (Box 254)
  - New England Regional Commission (Box 255)
    - Alternates Meeting, 1975 October 16 (Box 255)
    - Animal Export Facility at Bradley (Box 255)
    - Energy Programs (Box 255)
    - Energy Programs (Box 256)
    - Executive Session (Box 256)
    - Grants (Box 256)
    - Growth Center (Box 256)
    - Highlights (Box 256)
    - Meeting Agenda (Box 256)
    - Meeting July 24/Background Info (Box 256)
    - Minority Contractor (Box 256)
    - Minutes of Meeting, 1976 February 19 (Box 256)
    - Misc. (Box 257)
    - Misc. Material (Box 257)
    - NEBHE (Box 257)
    - Rail Planning Grant (Box 257)
    - Railroad Grant Agreement Between NERC & DOT (Box 257)
    - Task Force on Regional Labor and Capital Markets (Box 257)
  - New England Resource Agency (Box 257)
  - New England Resource Center for Occupational Education (Box 257)
  - New Englander (Box 257)
  - New Haven (Box 257)
  - New Haven Visit (Box 257)
  - New Horizons (Box 257)
  - Newington Home for Crippled Children (Box 257)
  - New York Fiscal Crisis (Box 257)
  - New York State (Box 257)
  - News Summaries (Box 258)
  - Nike Missile Base (Box 258)
  - Non-returnable bottles (B) (Box 258)
  - Norwich Office (Box 258)
  - Notary (Box 259)
  - Nuclear Power Plants #64 (B) (Box 259)
  - Nurse Practices Act SB 1485, Mag. Card (B), 1975 June 13 (Box 259)
  - Nursing (B) (Box 259)
  - Nursing Examiners (B) (Box 259)
  - Nursing Home (B) (Box 259)
  - Nursing Home: (Box 259)
    - Administrators (O) (Box 259)
    - Committee Mag. Card (O), 1975 November 3 (Box 259)
    - Committee Mag. Card (O), 1975 October 14 (Box 259)
    - Greenwood Nursing Home, Mag. #5 (B) (Box 260)
    - Investigation Blue Ribbon Committee (Box 260)
    - Legislation (Box 260)
    - Letters sent (O), 1976 February 23 (Box 260)
    - Letters sent to all Commissioners (O) (Box 260)
    - Mag. Letters sent to Nursing Blue Ribbon Committee (O) (Box 260)
    - Press Release from Governor’s Office (Box 260)
    - Reimbursement - Mag. #25 (B) (Box 260)
    - Rates & Care #5 Revised (Box 260)
    - Statements by Nursing Home Committee (Box 260)
    - Tx’s to Members of Blue Ribbon Committee to Investigate Nursing Home Industry (O) (Box 260)
    - (Box 260)
  - Nutmegger (Box 261)
  - OAS (Box 261)
  - O’Brian, John (Box 261)
  - Obscenity (Box 261)
  - Occupational Licensing/State Board for (Box 261)
  - Offerings (B) (Box 261)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity - OEO (Box 261)
  - OEO Grants (Box 261)
  - OEO Grants: (Box 261)
    - Meriden (Box 261)
  - OEO - Press releases from Governor’s Office (Box 261)
  - Office Hours (Box 261)
    - A, B (B) (Box 261)
    - C, D (B) (Box 261)
    - E, F (B) (Box 261)
    - G, H (B) (Box 261)
    - I, J, K (B) (Box 261)
    - L, M (B) (Box 261)
    - N, O, P (B) (Box 262)
    - Q, R (B) (Box 262)
    - S, T (B) (Box 262)
    - Buck to Miliano, Office of Policy Management #23, 1977 October (Box 262)
    - Milford (B) (Box 262)
    - Public Office Hours #7 (Box 262)
    - Stamford (B) (Box 262)
    - Winsted (B) (Box 262)
  - Office of Management & Budget (Box 262)
  - Office of Policy Management - OPM (Box 262)
    - A, B (B) (Box 262)
    - C, D (B) (Box 262)
    - E, F, G (Box 262)
    - H, I, J (B) (Box 262)
    - K, L (B) (Box 262)
    - M, N (B) (Box 262)
    - O, P, Q, R (B) (Box 262)
    - S, T (B) (Box 262)
    - U, V, W, X, Y, Z (B) (Box 262)
  - Office of Policy Management (Box 262)
    - Buck to Miliano, 1977 October (Box 262)
    - Memos to and from Miliano (Box 262)
  - Office of Technology Assessment (Federal) (Box 263)
  - Official Statements (B) (Box 263)
  - Oil (B) (Box 263)
  - Oil Conservation (Box 263)
  - Oil Import Tax (Box 263)
  - Oil Import Tax Letter (B) (Box 263)
  - Oil - Offshore Drilling (Box 264)
  - Oil Refineries (B) (Box 264)
  - Oil Refinery (B) (Box 264)
  - Oil Refinery #51 (O) (Box 264)
  - [Oil Refinery Task Force] (Box 264)
    - Organization/Questionnaire (Box 264)
    - Proposals Pending (Box 264)
    - Refinery Proposals (Box 264)
    - Responses Municipalities (I) (Box 264)
    - Responses - Organizations (Oil Refinery Input) (I) (Box 264)
  - Oil Support (B) (Box 264)
  - Oil Tankers, Mag. Card #68 (B) (Box 264)
  - Old Lime Visit (B) (Box 264)
  - Old State House Mag. Card (Box 264)
  - Ombudsman (Box 264)
  - O’Neill - Memos to (Box 264)
  - Opera Association (Box 264)
  - Opticians (B) (Box 264)
  - Optometry (B) (Box 264)
  - Optometry/Newspaper Ad Regarding the Delivery of Professional Vision (B) (Box 264)
    - Care/Mag. Card, 1977 November 2 (Box 264)
  - Organization and Management of the Executive Branch - Commission on (Box 264)
  - Organized Crime - prevention and Control (Box 264)
  - Outer Continental Shelf (Box 265)
  - Out of State School Project (B) (Box 265)
  - Pacesetter (Box 265)
  - Palestine (Box 265)
  - Panama Canal (B) (Box 265)
  - Partners of the Americas’ (Box 265)
  - Patronage (Box 265)
  - Penal Codes (B) (Box 265)
  - Pension Funds (B) (Box 265)
  - Periodicals (B) (Box 265)
  - Permit Examiner’s Board (B) (Box 265)
  - Perry Optical #2 (B) (Box 265)
  - Perry Optical #5 (B) (Box 265)
  - Personnel (Box 265)
    - A (B) (Box 265)
    - B (B) (Box 266)
    - C (B) (Box 266)
    - D (B) (Box 266)
    - E (B) (Box 267)
    - F (Box 267)
    - G (Box 267)
    - H (Box 267)
    - I, J (Box 267)
    - K (Box 267)
    - L (B) (Box 268)
    - M (B) (Box 268)
    - N (B) (Box 268)
    - O (B) (Box 268)
    - O, P (B) (Box 269)
    - Q, R (B) (Box 269)
    - S (B) (Box 269)
    - T (B) (Box 270)
    - U, V (B) (Box 270)
    - W (B) (Box 270)
    - X, Y, Z (B) (Box 270)
  - Personnel (Box 270)
    - Affirmative Action (Box 270)
    - Appeal Board (Box 270)
    - Appeal Board Appointments (O) (Box 270)
    - Bureau of Disability Determination (B) (Box 270)
    - Collective Bargaining (B) (Box 270)
    - Collective Bargaining/letter to Agency Heads Concerning (O) (Box 270)
    - Compensation for Elected Officials (Box 270)
    - Compensation plan (Box 270)
    - Conn. State Employees Association (CSEA) (B) (Box 270)
    - CSEA News (Box 271)
    - [Conn. State Employees Union] (Box 271)
      - AFL-CIO (Box 271)
      - AFSCME Council 18 (Box 271)
    - Defensive Driving Course (Box 271)
    - Employees Union (Box 271)
    - Emergency Employment Program (B) (Box 271)
    - Forty (40) Hour Week (B) (Box 271)
    - Forty (40) Hour Week/Mag. Letter (O) (Box 271)
    - Four (4) Day Work Week (B) (Box 271)
    - Griffenhagen Plan (B) (Box 271)
    - Holidays (B) (Box 271)
    - Interest in a Position/Mag. Card No. 8 (Box 271)
    - Intern Recommendations (Box 271)
    - Interns, Summer, 1977 (Box 271)
    - Internship (B) (Box 271)
    - Layoffs (B) (Box 271)
    - Layoff Mag. Card (Box 271)
    - Memos (Box 271)
    - Memos to and from Biloon (Box 272)
    - Memos to and from Phillips (Box 272)
    - Memos to and from Rossomando (Box 272)
    - Memos to and from Wnuk (Box 272)
    - Pending (B) (Box 272)
    - Policy Board (B) (Box 272)
    - Policy Board Agenda (Box 273)
    - Policy Board Appointment (O) (Box 273)
    - Press Releases from Governor’s Office (Box 273)
    - Salary Increases for State Employees - Mag. No. 57 (B) (Box 273)
    - State Employees (B) (Box 273)
    - State Employees Group Insurance (Box 273)
    - State Employees Group Insurance Commission (Box 273)
    - State Employees Raises - Letters Sent to Officials Who Voted it Approved (O) (Box 273)
    - State Employee Raises/ Use of Retirement Funds for Raises (B) (Box 273)
    - State Employee Raises #39 (B) (Box 273)
    - State Employee Retirement Benefits #66 (B) (Box 273)
    - State Employee Retirement Benefits #66 Revised (B) (Box 273)
    - State Employee Salaries (B) (Box 273)
    - State Raises Number 57A/letter to Non-State Employees (Box 273)
    - Suggestion Awards (B) (Box 273)
    - Summer Jobs (B) (Box 274)
    - Temporary Help (Box 274)
    - Toll Collector’s Meeting (Box 274)
  - Pharmacists (B) (Box 274)
  - Pharmacy Commission (B) (Box 274)